Privacy Policy
==============

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

MyBrowserAddon does NOT collect any personally identifiable information about You - such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address - unless You provide it to MyBrowserAddon voluntarily and approve its use.

If You do not want Your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to MyBrowserAddon. When You do provide MyBrowserAddon with personally identifiable information, it may use that information to better understand Your needs and how it can improve its products and services. MyBrowserAddon may also use that information to contact You, for example, to answer a question or respond to a comment You have submitted. MyBrowserAddon reserves the right to display any questions or comments You submit, without reference to your identity, together with any responses MyBrowserAddon provides, on its frequently asked questions page found at //mybrowseraddon.com/faq.html. In the case of requests for new pages, MyBrowserAddon will use Your information to assess Your request, to verify Your identity and the identity of Your other project contributors, and for any other reasonable purposes in connection with Your request. However, it will not provide Your information to third parties without your consent, except as required by law as explained in the "Information Sharing" section below.

In some cases, MyBrowserAddon may collect information that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system You use, the date and time You visited the Site, the pages You accessed, and the name of the website from which You linked to the Site. MyBrowserAddon uses this information to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**2\. Discussion and Social Plugins**

The site has a discussion section for conversions and comments about hosted projects and general issues related to browser applications and extension development. We use Facebook Comments Plugin for this purpose. To read more info about the privacy terms and conditions for the Facebook plugin please visit [this](https://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/comments/) link.

a. When participating in discussions, Your personal information may be publicly available through Your profile display, in which case You have the option to opt-out of publicly displaying Your real identity. Where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at Your discretion and may be changed at any time by You.

b. The Site is an open-source site and the data and information hosted on the site is publically accessible by design. Anonymous messages (or posts that have been edited to be made anonymous) are against the spirit of open-source. When You offer content for other MyBrowserAddon users to read, attaching Your name to it gives other MyBrowserAddon users the ability to reply to You privately about it, in case they feel that a public reply would be inappropriate. If You want to avoid spam, use mail filters, or refrain from posting on the Site. MyBrowserAddon will not be responsible for any unsolicited email that You receive as a result of You posting Your email address on the newsgroups, discussions, or mailing lists.

c. This privacy policy does not protect any information that You transmit to newsgroups, discussions, mailing lists, or other users.

**3\. Cookies**

MyBrowserAddon may use "cookies" - very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites - on the Site. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and will help MyBrowserAddon enhances its web experience by saving time on the Site. This can also make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. In general, cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience. With most Internet browsers, you can easily erase cookies from Your computer's hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, these may stop our website from functioning properly. Please refer to Your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions.

MyBrowserAddon may use cookies for the following reasons.

a. MyBrowserAddon allows you to share pages with some social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin, Google Plus, Pinterest, Stumbleupon, and GitHub. Each of these networks has its cookie policy. Please visit each social media website to see their cookie policies before sharing any content.

b. We also use Google Forms, Google Analytics and Google AdSense‎ in MyBrowserAddon. Google uses certain cookies to better operate on third-party websites. Please refer to how Google uses [cookies](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/), how Google uses [data](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/) when you use its partners sites or apps, how Google uses cookies in [advertising](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/) and Google [analytics](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage) cookie usage on websites to get more info about Google's policy about cookies.

c. MyBrowserAddon uses PayPal module to place PayPal donation button on its pages. PayPal website and its modules may use certain cookies in order to operate. Please read about PayPal policies about cookies [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full#How_We_Use_Cookies_and_Similar_Technologies).

d. MyBrowserAddon uses Amazon.com services such as cloud front (CDN). Amazon has certain cookie policies regarding its services. To read more about Amazon's cookie policy please visit Amazon.com [Privacy Notice](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496).

e. We also use Cloudflare CDN servers to host certain modules in MyBrowserAddon. This service may use certain cookies for different purposes. Please visit the following page to read more about the Cloudflare cookie policy. [more](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy)

**4\. Information Sharing**

Although MyBrowserAddon makes every effort to preserve user privacy, it may need to disclose information when required by law wherein it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on the Site.

**5\. Certain Third-Party Transactions**

MyBrowserAddon may disclose personal information to third parties it engages to provide services that involve data processing on its behalf. Also, if some or all of the assets of MyBrowserAddon are sold to a third party, such third party will be entitled to use the personal information disclosed by You, but only under the terms of this privacy statement.

**6\. Security**

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under MyBrowserAddon's control. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of the information You disclose Online since a sufficiently powerful attack from an unauthorized third party could compromise your data.

**7\. Links to Third-Party Sites**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that MyBrowserAddon is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. MyBrowserAddon encourages You to be aware when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site.

**8\. Contact**

If You have any questions or suggestions regarding MyBrowserAddon's privacy policy, or if You have submitted personally identifiable information through the Site and would like access to such information or to have that information corrected, please fill the contact form or send an email to support@mybrowseraddon.com
